{"Answer": "Effect of Screening Mammography on Breast-Cancer Mortality in Norway\n\nA challenge in quantifying the effect of screening mammography on breast-cancer mortality is to provide valid comparison groups . The use of historical control subjects does not take into account chronologic trends associated with advances in breast-cancer awareness and treatment .\n\nThe Norwegian breast-cancer screening program was started in 1996 and expanded geographically during the subsequent 9 years . Women between the ages of 50 and 69 years were offered screening mammography every 2 years . We compared the incidence-based rates of death from breast cancer in four groups : two groups of women who from 1996 through 2005 were living in counties with screening ( screening group ) or without screening ( nonscreening group ) ; and two historical-comparison groups that from 1986 through 1995 mirrored the current groups .\n\nWe analyzed data from 40,075 women with breast cancer . The rate of death was reduced by 7.2 deaths per 100,000 person-years in the screening group as compared with the historical screening group ( rate ratio , 0.72 ; 95 % confidence interval ( CI ) , 0.63 to 0.81 ) and by 4.8 deaths per 100,000 person-years in the nonscreening group as compared with the historical nonscreening group ( rate ratio , 0.82 ; 95 % CI , 0.71 to 0.93 ; P ( 0.001 for both comparisons ) , for a relative reduction in mortality of 10 % in the screening group ( P = 0.13 ) . Thus , the difference in the reduction in mortality between the current and historical groups that could be attributed to screening alone was 2.4 deaths per 100,000 person-years , or a third of the total reduction of 7.2 deaths .\n\nThe availability of screening mammography was associated with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer , but the screening itself accounted for only about a third of the total reduction . ( Funded by the Cancer Registry of Norway and the Research Council of Norway . )\n\n", "Topic": "breast", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes"], "norway": ["Participants"], "50 and 69": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "40,075": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "4.8": ["Outcomes"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "1996 through 2005": ["Intervention"], "nonscreen": ["Intervention"], "2.4": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "50 and 69": ["Age"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "4.8": ["Effect-strength"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "1996 through 2005": ["Duration"], "nonscreen": ["Control"], "2.4": ["Effect-strength"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Condition": [], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Sex": "The study was performed on women.", "Age": "The participants were between the ages of 50 and 69 years.", "Location": "The participants were from Norway.", "Sample-size": "The study analyzed data from 40075 participants.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the impact of screening mammography.", "Duration": "Participants were offered screening mammography every 2 years from 1996 to 2005.", "Control": "Participants in counties with screening were compared to participants in counties without screening, and with two historical groups.", "Outcomes-general": "The studied measure deaths from breast cancer.", "Effect-strength": "The relative reduction in mortality in the screening group was of 10%. The effect of screening in the reduction of deaths, when comparing with the historical groups, was of about a third of the total reduction (7.2 per 100,000 vs 4.8 per 100,000 person-years).", "Conclusion-general": "The availability of screening mammography was associated with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer, but the screening itself accounted for only about a third of the total reduction"}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography screening doesn't seem to have much affect on the breast cancer mortality rate in Norway. The challenge in quantifying the effects of mammograms on mortality was conducted in a nine year comparison study of over 40- thousand women aged 50 to 69 with breast cancer. They looked at the incidence in rates of death from the disease among those who had and had not been screened for breast cancer. The women were all offered a mammogram every two years. The data was analyzed between the two groups and showed the death rate was reduced by 7 deaths per 100,000 among those women in the screened group, and nearly 5 deaths in the non-screened group. This resulted in a relative reduction in mortality of 10% in the screening group. The differences suggest that the availability of screening was associated with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer, but the screening itself accounted for about a third of the total reduction. ", "AssignmentId": "3IO1LGZLKAIIPSYY8OJVP572LGE86L", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2KROBPV0YPE4A", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes"], "norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["B", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3IO1LGZLKAIIPSYY8OJVP572LGE86L", "children": [{"Answer": "The Norwegian Breast cancer screening program was started in 1996 and expanded geographically during the next 9 years. The program included women ages 50 to 69 who were offered screening mammograms every 2 years.  Norway wanted to compare incidence based deaths from breast cancer. They compared four groups of women. Two groups from counties that offered screening mammograms and 2 groups from historically gathered data. The reduction of 7.2 deaths out of 100,000 screenings were found. ", "AssignmentId": "3TEM0PF1Q6IZSC8AN7EU2WBCKLND0S", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["D", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["D"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3TEM0PF1Q6IZSC8AN7EU2WBCKLND0S", "children": [{"Answer": "A Norwegian breast cancer screening program was conducted for 9 years. The women studied were between 50 and 69 years of age and they were given screening mammograms every 2 years to see if it helped reduce breast cancer incidences. The mammography study proved it does help.", "AssignmentId": "3XLBSAQ9Z5XGDODQ0OO08342GQRZ7J", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"50 and 69": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"50 and 69": ["Age"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3XLBSAQ9Z5XGDODQ0OO08342GQRZ7J", "children": [{"Answer": "A Norwegian study shows that screening for breast cancer reduces the death rate, but was not the sole cause of the mortality reduction.", "AssignmentId": "3OJSZ2ATDTHI6AT1T0HKJZX7FWM75X", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3OJSZ2ATDTHI6AT1T0HKJZX7FWM75X", "children": [{"Answer": "A breast cancer study showed little reduction in death from screening.", "AssignmentId": "33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG6U0T85", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG6U0T85"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "This study was about the effects on screening mammography on breast cancer in Norway. The availability of screening mammography  which was offered a mammography screening every two years and has been associated with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer. The historical use of control subjects does not take into account chronologic trends associated with advances in breast cancer. The chronologic trends associated with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer, but the studys screening itself accounted for only about a third of the total reduction.  The program was started in 1996 in Norway and expanded in following years to other countries. There were approximately 40,000 aged between fifty through sixty nine women who took part in this study. The rate of death dropped by 7.2 per 100,000 people for the final result. This project was funded by the Cancer Registry of Norway and the research council of Norway.", "AssignmentId": "3RXPCZQMQQW2BL3JLGJ2MMXJ2VQG15", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3RXPCZQMQQW2BL3JLGJ2MMXJ2VQG15", "children": [{"Answer": "A Norwegian breast-cancer screening study compared four sets of women - two groups of women from 1996 to 2005 that lived in counties with screening or without screening - were compared to another two groups of women from 1986 to 1995. The study showed that the rate of death decreased for both screening and non-screening groups over time, and the availability of screening was also associated with reduced rate of death from breast cancer. However, the screening itself only accounted for a third of the total reduction between historical groups.", "AssignmentId": "30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9PO15Z5EY", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3LW4YHAM1JH1X", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9PO15Z5EY", "children": [{"Answer": "By reviewing data on over 40,000 Norwegian women with breast cancer and comparing contemporary groups with historical groups, researchers found that the availability of mammography screenings was connected with a reduction in the breast cancer death rate.", "AssignmentId": "3Q5ZZ9ZEVP0M6OYK359QXZT2QCX58F", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3Q5ZZ9ZEVP0M6OYK359QXZT2QCX58F", "children": [{"Answer": "After analyzing 40,074 women with breast cancer, it was found that screening mammography was associated with a reduced rate of death ", "AssignmentId": "3UOUJI6MTEZT64P7CETQLA2BG7WXU4", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3UOUJI6MTEZT64P7CETQLA2BG7WXU4", "children": [{"Answer": "Availability of mammography was associated with decreased rate of death.", "AssignmentId": "3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZV4RSRB", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZV4RSRB"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Screening mammography's usefulness in preventing breast cancer deaths is hard to gauge because it's hard to find good comparison groups. You can compare to older study groups but that wouldn't account for changes in technology that might affect mortality rates decreasing. The Norwegian breast cancer screening program started and grew, leading to women from 50-69 years old getting access to mammogram screenings every two years. They compared four groups made up of 40,075 women total with breast cancer. Two groups were from 1996-2005. One group received screening and one did not. The other two groups were from 1986 through 1995 and again, one received screening and the other didn't. The rate of death decreased by 7.2 deaths per 100,000 person-years in the 1996-2005 group compared to the 1986-1995 group. In women that didn't get screened, there was still a reduction of 4.8 deaths per 100,000 person-years. This concludes that screening did help reduce deaths but other factors helped with reduction of breast cancer deaths. ", "AssignmentId": "3KMS4QQVK3BY3MTAI6J29GT6ANJFK3", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1UI0SM8QV5IZ8", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "40,075": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "4.8": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "4.8": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3KMS4QQVK3BY3MTAI6J29GT6ANJFK3", "children": [{"Answer": "This  Norwegian based study on 40,000 women was to examine the availability of screening mammography with a reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer.  Screenings themself accounted for only about a third of the total reduction in the rate of death throughout the studied years. The study followed a group who was screened and also a group that was not screened. It was found that out of 100,000 people death had only occured an average of 7 times.", "AssignmentId": "3KRVW3HTZO62XFYZ92WHVS4POR1SMF", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3KRVW3HTZO62XFYZ92WHVS4POR1SMF", "children": [{"Answer": "Availability of screening mammography was associated with a reduction of death from breast cancer but, accounted for only about a third of the total reduction.  Use of historical control subjects does not take into account advances in breast-cancer awareness and treatment", "AssignmentId": "3CTOC39K38BQD98MI2LEK9GCXTI7JC", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2YTQDLACTLIBA", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "a third": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3CTOC39K38BQD98MI2LEK9GCXTI7JC", "children": [{"Answer": "Studies show that the availability of screening mammography showed a large reduction in the rate of death from breast cancer. ", "AssignmentId": "3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV8BN6Z90", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV8BN6Z90", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammogram screening is associated w/ lowering rate of death from breast ca", "AssignmentId": "37C0GNLMHGOU6NUPPWUBBXL3YE56DZ", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_37C0GNLMHGOU6NUPPWUBBXL3YE56DZ"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A Norwegian breast-cancer screening program that started in 1996 was expanded geographically during a subsequent 9 years. Women ages 50 to 69 yrs were offered screening mammograms every 2 yrs. They compared incidence-based rates of death from breast cancer in  2 group of women who from 1996 thru 2005 were living in counties w/ screening (screening group) or w/out (nonscreening group) and 2 historical-comparison groups that from 1986 thru 1995 mirrored the current group. Data was analyzed from 40075 women w/ breast cancer. The death rate was reduced by 7.2 deaths per 100,000 person-years in the nonscreen group as compared with the historical nonscreen group), for a relative reduction in mortality of 10% in the screening group. The difference in the reduction of mortality between the current and historical groups that could be attributed to screening alone was 2.4 deaths per 100,000 person-years. The availability of screening mammograms was associated w/ reducing the rate of death from breast cancer. The screening itself accounted for about 1/3 of the total reduction.", "AssignmentId": "340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q09DVUE", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "nonscreen": ["Intervention"], "2.4": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"], "rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "nonscreen": ["Control"], "2.4": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q09DVUE", "children": [{"Answer": "There is a challenging question as to how effective are mammograms in determining breast cancer mortality. In Norway, researchers started a screening program over a nine-year period comparing the incidence rates of death in women who had and had not been screened.  They concluded that the availability of screening mammography was associated with a reduction in the rate of death, but the screening itself accounted for only a third of the total reduction.", "AssignmentId": "31T4R4OBOT135V2G8A4SX53H7ZNC7X", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2KROBPV0YPE4A", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes"], "norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_31T4R4OBOT135V2G8A4SX53H7ZNC7X", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography can be a life saving measure to detect breast cancer. In a study, the group that was screened had a 10% reduction in mortality as opposed to the control. However, this only accounted for a third of the reduction in the rate of death. ", "AssignmentId": "3TU5ZICBREMBZAHINXXTVAOTM8EQ87", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2WNTEVRT68JXT", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"10 %": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"10 %": ["Effect-strength"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3TU5ZICBREMBZAHINXXTVAOTM8EQ87", "children": [{"Answer": "A norwegian study of 40,075 women with breast cancer was done.  After the study, it showed that mammography reduces breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "352YTHGROWYX3GVDS4KM5KGNT5IH43", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "40,075": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_352YTHGROWYX3GVDS4KM5KGNT5IH43", "children": [{"Answer": "In a Norway study, breast cancer screening isn't as useful as perceived.", "AssignmentId": "3KV0LJBBH36QW0YMUDWC5IZT3FDRM2", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "AXY0D2AMLKE2A", "Qualification": 0.5384615384615384, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3KV0LJBBH36QW0YMUDWC5IZT3FDRM2"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A study was performed in Norway to see if screening mammography would reduce the incidence of death from breast cancer.  Women between the ages of 50 and 69 years old were included in the study. They were screened every 2 years. The owmen were separated into 4 different groups. One group of women who lived in a countries with screening between 1996 and 2005, and a group of women who did not have screening in their country. Another study was performed on women that mirrored that study from 1986 to 1995. 40,075 women who had breast cancer were analyzed. Using screening methods the incidence of death from breast cancer was only 7.2 deaths per 100,00 person years.  This means that 2.4 women were saved from death by these screening procedures. Having mammography screening available to women was a major factor in reducing the incidence of breast cancer in women. The study showed that in Norway the reduction accounted for a 1/3 reduction in death.", "AssignmentId": "3KWTYT0871OHLVI3XUIU24F8AUK5LP", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "norway": ["Participants"], "50 and 69": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "40,075": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "2.4": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "50 and 69": ["Age"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "2.4": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3KWTYT0871OHLVI3XUIU24F8AUK5LP", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography screening has reduced the death rate in women with breast cancer. 40,075 women were studied in 4 groups, the first 2 in the years of 1986 to 1995 and the last 2 from 1996 to 2005. In both studies the participants were a part of either a screening group or a non screening group. Every 2 years the screening group patients were given a screening mammography, and the patients in the non screening group were not. The results showed that death rate was reduced by 4.8 out of 100,000 compared with the screening group at 7.2 out of 100,000. ", "AssignmentId": "37TRT2X24RCDFLBCVJXUPB28G9XBJ6", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "40,075": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "4.8": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "4.8": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_37TRT2X24RCDFLBCVJXUPB28G9XBJ6", "children": [{"Answer": "Biennial screening Mammography reduces mortality in women with breast cancer. In Norway, the mortality in women with breast cancer dropped 10% for patients who got screened. Out of 100,000 women, those screened had 7.2 less deaths then the control group at 4.8 less deaths. ", "AssignmentId": "3MTMREQS4W3U2V6JW4GDJQCA0X7WAX", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "ADGH08WUP68ZF", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "4.8": ["Outcomes"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "4.8": ["Effect-strength"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3MTMREQS4W3U2V6JW4GDJQCA0X7WAX", "children": [{"Answer": "The rate of death reduced by 7.2 deaths in the screening group as opposed to the non screening group which was reduced by 4.8 deaths. ", "AssignmentId": "3UN61F00HXASOTDG2EFQOGO7GA55RN", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2YUCJ28XANFOX", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"7.2": ["Outcomes"], "4.8": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "4.8": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3UN61F00HXASOTDG2EFQOGO7GA55RN", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography availability reduced rate of death from breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3QEMNNSB2YKDAN8U86Z3HBLZTPR7D1", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3QEMNNSB2YKDAN8U86Z3HBLZTPR7D1"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "The breast cancer screening program in Norway was started in 1996 to counteract the challenge of determining the efficacy of mammograms in terms of death from the disease on equal groups. Using past data was never helpful as it did not take into account things like then-current advances in breast cancer treatment and awareness. The Norwegian program offered women between the ages of 50 and 69 a mammogram every two years. They compared the results with similar groups of women who lived in other countries that provided screening, similar groups of women who lived in countries without screening and two historical groups that had similar experiences with screenings. They analyzed data from over 40,000 women with cancer of the breast. In all women who had screenings, the mortality rate was reduced by 7.2 deaths per 100,000 people. This reduced the death rate by 10%. This showed that screening does reduce the risk of death. ", "AssignmentId": "33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG6YGT8T", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3HEDIGLDT2NF3", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "50 and 69": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "50 and 69": ["Age"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_33L7PJKHCHJORQ9A41RO0FZG6YGT8T", "children": [{"Answer": "This was a study that compared four groups of 40,075 women, one group was screened for breast cancer between 1996-2005, the other group was screened between the years of 1986-1995, the other two groups had no screening. the women that were screened were between the ages of 50-69, they were offered screening every 2 years from 1986-2005. When the data from these 40,075 women was analyzed, it showed that in total women who were screened had a 10% reduction in mortality.", "AssignmentId": "3PQMUDRV7SRR7I5CJB4BZXRLYL6IIQ", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3CDWPBKYDDASL", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "40,075": ["Participants"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "40,075": ["Sample-size"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3PQMUDRV7SRR7I5CJB4BZXRLYL6IIQ", "children": [{"Answer": "In this content they show the result of breast cancer patients totally 40075 had cancer,they watched very closely,and the rate of death is 7.2 of 100,000 person due to this mammography the rate of death is reduced.this is funded by cancer registry of Norway", "AssignmentId": "3N2BF7Y2VRFD76KJY8KIREXNFRZHMK", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1RVRSK2GTUVGK", "Qualification": 0.5384615384615384, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3N2BF7Y2VRFD76KJY8KIREXNFRZHMK", "children": [{"Answer": "In Norway a study showed a 10% reduction in breast cancer mortality in geographic groups having greater screening availablity.", "AssignmentId": "3NQL1CS15STIJO4HM0PX0AB3WM3VY5", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1E235KE3CSO7H", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes"], "norway": ["Participants"], "10 %": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"breast cancer mortality": ["Outcomes-general"], "norway": ["Location"], "10 %": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3NQL1CS15STIJO4HM0PX0AB3WM3VY5", "children": [{"Answer": "the breast cancer is most dangerous disease in the world.", "AssignmentId": "33CUSNVVNOX5T6HM13GT9J3TTI288L", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["C", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_33CUSNVVNOX5T6HM13GT9J3TTI288L"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A study that took place in Norway found that making mammography screening available to women between the ages of 50 and 90 every two years had an impact on the rate of breast cancer deaths. To verify the data, it was compared to women who lived in a place where no mammography screening was available, and then compared to older data from both types of groups (women who lived where screening was available and those who did not). The total reduction of deaths from the recent group who lived in an area when mammography screening was made available was 7.2 less deaths per year. Unfortunately the overall comparison revealed that the availability of screening alone only contributed to 2.4 less deaths per year.  &#13;Although the impact of having mammography screening available to residents of a country makes only a slight impact on the number of breast cancer deaths per year, it is still an impact, and should not be discounted. ", "AssignmentId": "3WMOAN2SRCIO7P03FYGMJUDWSF6VNC", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "AUPHYAKC58LPA", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "2.4": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "2.4": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "D", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["D"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3WMOAN2SRCIO7P03FYGMJUDWSF6VNC", "children": [{"Answer": "It is a struggle when trying to analyze trends for breast cancer research. This is because some of the data used is now out dated, and we now have technology such as mammogram machines. Norway started a breast cancer screening program in the 90s and it grew from there. The older women were given mammograms every couple of years. After analyzing data, the death rate decreased by a little over 7%. These screening programs are vital and we need them everywhere.", "AssignmentId": "3D8YOU6S9F5GNP5BBRK0LXPRJP76U1", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "AHYXP6QIMYJLD", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "D"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["D"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3D8YOU6S9F5GNP5BBRK0LXPRJP76U1", "children": [{"Answer": "we analysed data from 40075 women with breast cancer. the rate of death was reduced by 7.2 deaths per 100000 persons in year.screening mammography was reduced the rate of breast cancer but only about a third of the total reduction", "AssignmentId": "36ZN444YTSJ134GFH6HGJUN7A4XIOX", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "7.2": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"screen mammography": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "7.2": ["Effect-strength"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_36ZN444YTSJ134GFH6HGJUN7A4XIOX", "children": [{"Answer": "Since the start of the breast-cancer screening program in Norway the number of deaths in women aged 50 to 69 years has decreased. ", "AssignmentId": "3B2X28YI3X01RQW5B035G7X3ULD6BV", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A329WHNJKAKTW7", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3B2X28YI3X01RQW5B035G7X3ULD6BV", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammography screening reduces the rate of breast cancer deaths.", "AssignmentId": "3LRLIPTPERU37VC27QXAVFIFE6WAKA", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A3P57IUDHUKNCE", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3LRLIPTPERU37VC27QXAVFIFE6WAKA"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "A breast-cancer screening program in Norway has published its results on the effect of breast-cancer screening on mortality rates of breast cancer. This study was deemed necessary as there is some difficulty in finding comparison groups. The study began in 1996 and expanded in the coming 9 years. During this time, women fitting certain criteria were offered screening every two years and four comparison groups were formed. They were women who lived in counties where screening had been offered and not offered during the trial period, and two similar groups that were formed ten years previous to the forming of these groups. Data from 40, 075 women was analyzed and it was found among both the current and historical group that those offered breast cancer screening saw a decrease in mortality rates of about a third. This was a reduction of about 2.4 people in every 100,000. This has shown that offering breast cancer screening can impact the mortality rate of breast cancer.", "AssignmentId": "3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLWBMA29", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1TMWYZL6USNIF", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"norway": ["Participants"], "woman": ["Participants"], "2 year": ["Intervention"], "2.4": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"norway": ["Location"], "woman": ["Sex"], "2 year": ["Duration"], "2.4": ["Effect-strength"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLWBMA29", "children": [{"Answer": "A Norwegian breast-cancer screening prgrm started in 1996 &amp; expanded geographically during the 9 yrs. Women btwn ages 50 &amp; 69 were offered a mammogram every 2 yrs. Incidence based rates of death frm breast cancer were compared in 4 grps of 40075 wmn w/ breast cancer: 2 grps from 1996-2005 living in countries w/ screening or w/out screening; &amp; 2 historical comparison grps from 1986-1995 that mirrored current grps. The availability to screening was associated w/ reducing rate of death, but screening itself only accounted for abt 1/3 of reduction.", "AssignmentId": "3S0TNUHWKU3HA1DDIBR9VBHU3KGD8Y", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"woman": ["Participants"], "historical": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"woman": ["Sex"], "historical": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": ["A"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3S0TNUHWKU3HA1DDIBR9VBHU3KGD8Y", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammogram screenings are associated with a reduction in the rate of deaths from breast cancer, but differences in control groups of various studies may also account for some of the reduced deaths. Screening alone accounts for about a third of the total reduction.", "AssignmentId": "3P529IW9KZ69NSBS36V3OG6LZ8VFLJ", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A83OOIGU4606R", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"], "a third": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"], "a third": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3P529IW9KZ69NSBS36V3OG6LZ8VFLJ", "children": [{"Answer": "Norwegian researched showed the availability of mammograms did lower the rate of breast cancer deaths, but the screening itself did not.", "AssignmentId": "378XPAWRUDYC10ME7NCYIZ32LUSAI3", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A2JFK6KAWDU0KA", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "B", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_378XPAWRUDYC10ME7NCYIZ32LUSAI3", "children": [{"Answer": "Mammograms reduced the rate of death from breast cancers.", "AssignmentId": "3B2X28YI3X01RQW5B035G7X3VTW6BV", "Question": "NEJMoa1000727", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "breast", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1000727", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rate of death from breast cancer": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Age": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1000727_3B2X28YI3X01RQW5B035G7X3VTW6BV"}]}]}]}]}]}